Finding Aid for Suomi College Finnish-American collection, 1880-1972
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Finnish-American Collection: Church Records, Labor Societies, Temperance Organizations, and others
  - The Archive of the Historical Museum in Kaleva, Michigan
    - History (Youth or Nouriso Society) (Reel 24)
    - Minute book (Kalevatar)
      - January 12, 1902-October 21, 1905 (Reel 24)
      - November 4, 1906-February 24, 1907 (Reel 25)
    - Diary of Johan Jouppi (Kaleva, Mich.) 1911-1916 (Reel 25)
    - Membership book No. I (Kaleva Finnish Church) (Reel 25)
    - Membership book No. II (Kaleva Finnish Church) (Reel 25)
    - Minute book (Kaleva Finnish Church)
      - January 12, 1902-April 19, 1931 (Reel 25)
      - July 12, 1931-October 10, 1948 (Reel 25)
    - Account book 1939-1948 (Kaleva Finnish Church) (Reel 26)
    - Minute book 1933-1947 (Christian Youth Association Koitto [Dawn], Kaleva, Mich.) (Reel 26)
    - Paimensanomia [Shepherd News] 1922-1928 (religious periodical), Printed in Hancock, Mich. (Reel 26)
    - Lasten lehti [Children's Paper] 1922, 1927-1928. Printed in Hancock, Mich. (Reel 26)
    - Finnish Almanac 1913 (Reel 26)
    - Joululehti [Christmas Paper] 1916. Printed in Hancock, Mich. (Reel 26)
    - Siirtolainen [Immigrant] June 7, 1904. Finnish newspaper, published in Kaleva, Mich. (Reel 26)
    - The American Weekly October 27, 1940- November 3, 1940, November 17, 1940 (Reel 26)
    - The Grand Rapids Herald July 1, 1951 (Reel 26)
    - The Manistee County Pioneer Press (scattered dates) (Reel 26)
    - The Bear Lake Beacon November 17, 1916 (Reel 26)
    - Early History of Kaleva (clippings) (Reel 26)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Waukegan, Illinois
    - Membership book No. I (Reel 26)
    - Confirmations 1907-1928 (Reel 26)
    - Membership book No. II (Reel 26)
    - Baptisms 1912-1949 (Reel 26)
    - Confirmations 1913-1948 (Reel 26)
    - Marriages 1912-1947 (Reel 26)
    - Dismissal of members (Reel 26)
    - Funerals 1912-1948 (Reel 26)
    - Baptisms 1949-1970 (Reel 26)
    - Confirmations 1949-1970 (Reel 26)
    - Burials 1949-1970 (Reel 26)
    - Marriages 1947-1970 (Reel 26)
    - Church treasurers (Reel 26)
    - Sunday school superintendents (Reel 26)
    - Festivals (Reel 26)
    - Church secretaries (Reel 26)
    - Baptisms 1895-1897 (Reel 27)
    - Confirmations 1896-1897 (Reel 27)
    - Marriages 1896-1901 (Reel 27)
    - Funerals 1895-1901 (Reel 27)
    - Minute books
      - December 17, 1893-December 12, 1909 (official meetings) (Reel 27)
      - August 8, 1912-March 18, 1917 (church council) (Reel 27)
      - April 2, 1917-September 8, 1922 (church council) (Reel 27)
      - March 26, 1917-October 9, 1917 (deacons) (Reel 27)
      - October 13, 1922-January 1, 1926 (church council) (Reel 27)
      - February 12, 1926-March 13, 1930 (church council) (Reel 27)
      - July 5, 1935-October 1, 1942 (church council) (Reel 27)
    - Membership book 1926-1950 (Reel 27)
    - Membership book 1926-1950 (cont) (Reel 28)
    - Minute books
      - March 26, 1913-December 4, 1927 (sewing circle) (Reel 28)
      - January 20, 1915-October 30, 1918 (sewing circle) (Reel 28)
      - July 12, 1944-January 28, 1954 (sewing circle) (Reel 28)
      - September 20, 1931-December 24, 1942 (Sunday school) (Reel 28)
      - September 5, 1946-June 5, 1947 (sewing circle) (Reel 28)
      - June 19, 1947-December 1, 1949 (sewing circle) (Reel 29)
      - September 28, 1930-June 6, 1931 (church choir) (Reel 29)
    - Minute book and cash book July 3, 1898-1912 (building committee) (Reel 29)
    - Minute book
      - October 13, 1942-January 26, 1949 (church council) (Reel 29)
    - Cash book 1931-1947 (Reel 29)
    - Minute Book
      - September 21, 1932-December 3, 1945 (teachers) (Reel 29)
      - January 13, 1938-April 23, 1946 (Luther League) (Reel 29)
    - Birth certificates from Finland (Reel 29)
    - Rules of the congregation (Reel 29)
    - Minute book October 16, 1917-May 15, 1932 (Sunday school) (Reel 29)
    - Cash book
      - 1897-1913 (building committee) (Reel 29)
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - January 12, 1941-July 24, 1953 (Reel 29)
      - October 29, 1953 (Reel 30)
  - The Archive of Mr. Alex Kyyhkynen (Duluth, Minnesota), the former Honorary Consul of Finland
    - Brief biographies (Reel 30)
    - Questionnaires (Reel 30)
    - Minute book (Help Finland Knitting Club)
      - October 21, 1940-June 4, 1948 (Reel 30)
    - Questionnaires (Reel 30)
    - Correspondence 1946-1951 (Finnish-American Historical Society of Minnesota) (Reel 30)
    - Minute book
      - May 13, 1948-March 31, 1950 (Finnish-American Historical Society of Minnesota) (Reel 30)
    - Meetings of the Historical Society 1948 (Reel 30)
    - Minnesotan Suomalais-Amerikkalaisen Historiallisen Seuran Perus-ja Sivusäännöt [The Rules of the Finnish American Historical Society of Minnesota]. Printed (Reel 30)
    - Meetings of the Historical Society 1946-1948 (Reel 30)
    - Correspondence 1946-1951 (Historical Society) (Reel 30)
    - Clippings (Reel 30)
    - Correspondence of the Historical Society 1946-1950 (Reel 31)
    - Clippings (Reel 31)
    - Correspondence of the Historical Society 1946-1951 (Reel 31)
    - Meetings of the Historical Society 1954 (Reel 31)
    - Correspondence of the Historical Society 1953-1955 (Reel 31)
    - Bills, membership lists etc. (Historical Society) (Reel 31)
    - Preliminary plans for publishing the book The History of Minnesota Finns (Reel 31)
    - Interviews, brief histories of Finnish towns in Minnesota (Reel 31)
    - Correspondence of the Historical Society 1960-1964 (Reel 31)
    - Meetings of the Historical Society 1963-1970 (Reel 31)
  - Finnish Workers Association of Cloquet, Minnesota
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - February 22, 1911-October 28, 1917 (Reel 31)
    - Cash book 1919-1920 (Reel 31)
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - February 9, 1919-September 9, 1924 (Reel 31)
  - Finnish. Lutheran Congregation of Girard, Ohio
    - Minute book (official meetings) (Reel 32)
      - January 1, 1909-April 10, 1927 (Reel 32)
  - Temperance Society Pyrintö [Aspiration], Coal Centers, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - January 5, 1904-May 28, 1911 (Reel 32)
  - Temperance Society Voiton Lippu [The Flag of Victory], Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - April 12, 1903-February 26, 1905 (Reel 32)
    - Annual Report 1912-1931 (Reel 32)
  - Temperance Society Rauhan Alku [The Beginning of Peace], Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Woiton Kaiku [The Echo of Victory] Handwritten paper 1919 (Reel 32)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Nanty Glo, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book
      - September 11, 1902-January 1, 1924 (Reel 32)
      - January 1, 1924-January 20, 1946 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance Society Ilmarinen, Cloquet, Minnesota
    - Minute book
      - October 12, 1918-October 3, 1948 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance Society Toivon Tähti [The Star of Hope], Duluth, Minnesota
    - Letters (Reel 33)
    - Minute books
      - April 14, 1931-May 16, 1931 (Reel 33)
      - February 3, 1929-May 16, 1931 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance League of Marquette County, Michigan
    - Minute books
      - April 9, 1907-December 8, 1912 (Reel 33)
      - February 2, 1913-September 5, 1920 (Reel 33)
      - September 18, 1921-September 14, 1924 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance Society Onnela [Place of Happiness], Iron Mountain, Michigan
    - Minute book
      - May 5, 1899-September 24, 1899 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance League of Iron County, Michigan
    - Minute book April 12, 1907-October 28, 1917 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance League of Illinois
    - Minute book
      - September 9, 1911-March 16, 1919 (Reel 33)
      - June 28, 1919-November 28, 1954 (Reel 33)
  - Temperance Society Voiton Lippu [The Flag of Victory], Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book
      - September 8, 1918-August 22, 1920 (Reel 34)
  - Temperance Society Toivon Liitto [The Alliance of Hope], Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Membership book (Reel 34)
    - Minute book
      - September 1, 1907-May 5, 1915 (Reel 34)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Rankin, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book
      - May 1, 1904-April 13, 1934 (Reel 34)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Walston, Pennsylvania
    - Membership book (Reel 34)
    - Baptisms 1904-1906 (Reel 34)
    - Minute book
      - March 20, 1904-July 17, 1906 (Reel 34)
  - Temperance Society Onnen Koitto [The Dawn of Happiness], West Concord, New Hampshire
    - Minute book
      - September 30, 1906-June 10, 1918 (Reel 34)
      - July 14, 1918-February 2, 1919 (Reel 34)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of New Castle, Pennsylvania
    - Brief history of the church (Reel 34)
    - Minute book
      - January 16, 1914-April 30, 1917 (Reel 34)
      - December 3, 1900-November 27, 1914 (Reel 34)
  - Temperance Society Uusi Toivo [New Hope], New Castle, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book (Reel 35)
      - September 18, 1921-November 19, 1932 (Reel 35)
  - Temperance Society Kalevan Miekka [The Sword of Kaleva], Montreal, Wisconsin
    - Minute book
      - May 9, 1890-October 4, 1891 (Reel 35)
      - April 29, 1906-October 22, 1911 (Reel 35)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Iron Belt, Wisconsin
    - Minute book
      - January 3, 1936-January 29, 1950 (Reel 36)
  - Temperance Society Kasvi [Plant], Fairport Harbor, Ohio
    - Minute books
      - September 13, 1896-August 6, 1899 (Reel 36)
      - August 13, 1899-March 8, 1903 (Reel 36)
      - March 15, 1903-April 8, 1906 (Reel 36)
      - April 15, 1906-October 8, 1906 (Reel 37)
      - November 4, 1906-February 20, 1910 (Reel 37)
      - February 27, 1910-November 6, 1910 (Reel 37)
      - May 31, 1914-February 18, 1917 (Reel 37)
      - March 11, 1917-November 14, 1920 (Reel 37)
      - December 5, 1920-February 10, 1924 (Reel 37)
      - October 12, 1924-November 17, 1929 (Reel 38)
      - December 1, 1929-May 17, 1953 (Reel 38)
    - Rules (Reel 38)
  - Temperance Society Suomi [Finland], Astoria, Oregon
    - Minute book
      - January 29, 1903-April 30, 1903 (Reel 38)
  - Temperance Society Alku [Beginning], Maynard, Massachusetts
    - Minute books (board of directors)
      - March 30, 1909-March 5, 1922 (Reel 39)
      - March 26, 1922-December 23, 1930 (Reel 39)
      - January 12, 1931-January 5, 1937 (Reel 39)
      - February 4, 1937-December 3, 1950 (Reel 39)
      - February 4, 1951-May 23, 1961 (Reel 39)
    - Minute books (official meetings)
      - September 5, 1909-January 5, 1913 (Reel 39)
      - January 5, 1913-May 18, 1913 (Reel 39)
      - May 18, 1913-August 30, 1914 (Reel 40)
      - September 6, 1914-June 1916 (Reel 40)
      - June 25, 1916-January 10, 1918 (Reel 40)
      - April 28, 1935-December 18, 1938 (Reel 40)
      - January 15, 1939-January 7, 1951 (Reel 40)
      - January 21, 1951-November 14, 1954 (Reel 40)
      - September 15, 1957-August 9, 1967 (Reel 41)
    - A brief history of the society 1895-1935 (Reel 41)
    - Minute books
      - 1942 (Aid for Finland [during the Second World War]) (Reel 41)
      - 1922-1925 (young men's club) (Reel 41)
    - Minute books (official meetings)
      - 1895-1898 (Reel 41)
      - 1898-1901 (Reel 41)
      - 1901-1904 (Reel 41)
      - 1904-1905 (Reel 41)
      - 1905-1907 (Reel 42)
      - 1907-1909 (Reel 42)
      - 1918-1924 (Reel 42)
      - 1924-1929 (Reel 42)
      - 1929-1935 (Reel 42)
  - Temperance Society Riento [Active], Monson, Maine
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - January 1, 1908-July 26, 1914 (Reel 42)
  - Temperance Society Roihu [Flame], Coburntown, Michigan
    - Rules (Reel 42)
    - Minute book
      - February 15, 1934-March 9, 1934 (Reel 42)
      - March 23, 1934-October 19, 1955 (Reel 43)
  - Eastern Conference of Suomi Synod Lutheran Guild
    - Minute book
      - April 11, 1954-April 8, 1961 (Reel 43)
      - April 4, 1949-April 20, 1952 (Reel 43)
      - October 3, 1959-October 19, 1962 (Bible Camp Board) (Reel 43)
      - March 8, 1953-December 11, 1959 (Reel 43)
      - February 19, 1960-November 2, 1962 (Reel 43)
  - Finnish Club of Quincy, Massachusetts
    - Minute book
      - May 7, 1940-October 30, 1958 (Reel 43)
    - Letters (Reel 43)
  - Temperance Society Apilan Kukka [Blossom of Clover], Rudyard, Michigan
    - Minute book
      - March 30, 1908-August 8, 1909 (Reel 43)
  - Temperance Society Onnen Satama [Harbor of Happiness], Covington, Michigan
    - Minute book
      - November 25, 1906-January 7, 1917 (Reel 43)
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - December 28, 1921-August 4, 1934 (Reel 44)
      - February 3, 1937-June 1, 1958 (Reel 44)
    - Minute book (board of directors)
      - January 20, 1945-January 21, 1969 (Reel 44)
      - July 15, 1958-July 19, 1970 (Reel 44)
    - Account book 1956-1964 (Reel 44)
    - A brief history of the association (Reel 45)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Worcester, Massachusetts
    - Membership book (Reel 45)
    - Membership book (Reel 45)
    - Baptisms 1893-1906 (Reel 45)
    - Confirmations 1893-1906 (Reel 45)
    - Marriages 1893-1906 (Reel 45)
    - Reception of members 1894-1906 (Reel 45)
    - Funerals 1893-1906 (Reel 45)
    - Baptisms 1907-1921 (Reel 45)
    - Confirmations 1907-1932 (Reel 45)
    - Marriages 1907-1934 (Reel 45)
    - Baptisms 1921-1928 (Reel 45)
    - Funerals 1908-1935 (Reel 45)
    - Minute books (church council)
      - January 31, 1904-February 1, 1914 (Reel 45)
      - May 5, 1928-January 2, 1937 (official meetings) (Reel 45)
    - Annual report 1936 (Reel 46)
    - Minute books (official meetings)
      - February 6, 1937-December 7, 1940 (Reel 46)
      - January 11, 1941-January 8, 1955 (Reel 46)
      - April 2, 1955-September 7, 1967 (Reel 46)
    - Minute books (board of directors)
      - January 3, 1929-October 21, 1946 (Reel 46)
    - Minute books (board of trustees)
      - January 30, 1932-September 29, 1945 (Reel 46)
      - October 27, 1945-July 15, 1953 (Reel 46)
      - September 25, 1953-January 31, 1958 (Reel 47)
    - Minute books
      - September 19, 1947-February 25, 1963 (men's club) (Reel 47)
      - January 25, 1951-February 14, 1957 (sewing circle) (Reel 47)
      - January 25, 1956-November 14, 1958 (sewing circle) (Reel 47)
    - Cash book 1906-1917 (sewing circle) (Reel 47)
    - Cash books (church)
      - 1897-1905 (Reel 47)
      - 1932-1935 (Reel 47)
      - 1952-1960 (Reel 47)
    - List of persons who have loaned money to the church
      - 1918 (Reel 47)
      - 1937 (Reel 47)
      - 1937 (cont.) (Reel 48)
  - Kalevan Ritarit [The Knights of Kaleva], Fitchburg, Massachusetts
    - First meeting January 31, 1908 (Reel 48)
    - Reports of the meetings 1908-1960 (Reel 48)
    - Minute book
      - November 22, 1939-January 14, 1942 (Aid for Finland, during the Second World War) (Reel 48)
    - Kalevaisten 50-vuotisjuhlajulkaisu 1898-1948 [The 50th Anniversary of the Knights and the Ladies of Kaleva]. Printed. (Reel 48)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Gardner, Massachusetts
    - Golden Jubilee 1893-1943. Finnish Evangelical Lutheran Church. Printed (in English) (Reel 48)
    - Rules of the church. Printed in Hancock, Michigan. (Reel 48)
    - Suomi-Synodin kiertokirje No: 23 [Newsletter of Suomi Synod N:o23]. Printed in Hancock, Mich. 1909 (Reel 48)
    - Suomi-Synodin kiertokirje No:24 [Newsletter of Suomi Synod N:o24]. Printed in Hancock, Mich. 1910 (Reel 48)
    - Membership book (started in 1903) (Reel 48)
  - Finnish Congregational Church of Maynard, Massachusetts
    - Membership book (Reel 48)
    - Membership book (started in 1932) (Reel 48)
    - Baptisms 1912-1965 (Reel 48)
    - Marriages 1912-1964 (Reel 48)
    - Funerals 1960-1965 (Reel 48)
    - Funerals 1949 (Reel 48)
    - Funerals 1912-1940 (Reel 48)
    - Funerals 1940-1960 (Reel 49)
    - Confirmations 1912-1966 (Reel 49)
  - Finnish Workers Association of Newport, New Hampshire
    - Minute book February 2, 1911-June 15, 1919 (Agitation Committee) (Reel 49)
    - Rules 1911 (Reel 49)
    - Minute books (official meetings)
      - August 8, 1912-September 20, 1913 (Reel 49)
      - September 24, 1913-June 27, 1915 (Reel 49)
      - July 1, 1915-June 11, 1916 (Reel 49)
      - June 18, 1916-April 26, 1917 (Reel 49)
      - April 28, 1917-January 28, 1918 (Reel 49)
      - December 3, 1918-February 12, 1920 (Reel 50)
      - February 15, 1920-May 28, 1925 (Reel 50)
      - May 31, 1925-November 22, 1928 (Reel 50)
      - November 25, 1928-November 5, 1933 (Reel 51)
      - September 4, 1961-December 3, 1961 (Reel 51)
    - Minute books
      - December 5, 1909-December 19, 1911 (building committee) (Reel 51)
      - December 9, 1905-May 1, 1911 (entertainment committee) (Reel 51)
      - August 7, 1919-January 22, 1922 (entertainment committee) (Reel 51)
      - December 18, 1911-August 5, 1912 (bazaar committee) (Reel 51)
    - The book of the library (Reel 51)
    - The book of the library (cont) (Reel 52)
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - February 11, 1962-June 18, 1967 (Reel 52)
    - Membership book (Reel 52)
    - Minute book
      - August 4, 1913-September 7, 1950 (official meetings and entertainment committee) (Reel 52)
    - Photographs (Reel 52)
  - Finnish Congregational Church. of Troy, New Hampshire
    - Minute book (official meetings)
      - January 7, 1918-January 24, 1959 (Reel 52)
    - Membership book (Reel 52)
    - Cash books
      - 1951-1959 (Reel 52)
      - 1910-1944 (Reel 52)
      - 1916-1935 (Reel 52)
      - 1935-1944 (Reel 53)
      - 1944-1971 (Reel 53)
  - Temperance Society Toivo [Hope], Wakefield, Michigan
    - Minute book
      - July 21, 1889-August 16, 1891 (Reel 53)
      - June 6, 1909-June 30, 1912 (Reel 53)
      - February 12, 1934-December 10, 1934 (Reel 53)
      - April 26, 1937-April 3, 1939 (Reel 53)
      - May 2, 1939-September 14, 1941 (Reel 53)
      - October 27, 1941-November 8, 1943 (Reel 53)
      - November 29, 1943-November 11, 1946 (Reel 53)
      - November 18, 1946-February 4, 1952 (Reel 53)
  - Help Finland Materials from Michigan (during the Second World War)
    - Correspondence (Reel 54)
    - Accounts (Reel 54)
    - Reports (Reel 54)
    - Plans (Reel 54)
    - Minute book (Detroit's Lotta Svärd organization)
      - January 22, 1940-November 18, 1940 (Reel 54)
    - Cash book 1940 (Detroit's Lotta Svärd Organization) (Reel 54)
    - Minutebook
      - November 18, 1940-February 14, 1946 (Detroit) (Reel 54)
    - Annual report 1940-1941 (Detroit) (Reel 54)
    - Cash book 1940 (Detroit) (Reel 54)
    - Minute book
      - December 31, 1939-August 6, 1941 (Amasa, Mich.) (Reel 54)
    - Letters (Reel 54)
    - Minute books
      - 1940-1948 (Negaunee, Mich.) (Reel 54)
      - (Bovey, Minnesota) (Reel 54)
      - (Crystal Falls, Mich.) (Reel 54)
    - Letters (Reel 55)
    - Lists of donations (Reel 55)
    - Minute books from various places (mainly from Michigan) (Reel 55)
    - Accounts (Reel 55)
    - Reports (Reel 55)
  - The Illness Aid Organization of Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Minute books
      - 1908-1914 (Reel 55)
      - August 16, 1936-July 23, 1944 (Baltimore Chapter) (Reel 55)
      - March 19, 1953-June 17, 1956 (Baltimore Chapter) (Reel 55)
  - Temperance Society Suomen Ruusu [The Rose of Finland], Cleveland, Ohio
    - Minute book
      - January 8, 1905-March 11, 1906 (Reel 56)
      - July 2, 1911-January 18, 1914 (Reel 56)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Glassport, Pennsylvania
    - Minute book
      - January 4, 1903-April 26, 1914 (Reel 56)
  - Temperance Society Vesa [Sprout], Glassport, Pennsylvania
    - Minute books
      - October 19, 1902-August 21, 1904 (Reel 56)
      - August 27, 1904-April 1, 1906 (Reel 56)
      - April 1, 1906-July 17, 1910 (Reel 56)
      - July 24, 1910-September 29, 1912 (Reel 56)
      - October 6, 1912-June 8, 1913 (Reel 57)
  - Temperance Society Tähti [Star], New York, N.Y.
    - Minute Books
      - 1896-1900 (Reel 57)
      - 1901-1908 (Reel 57)
      - September 13, 1908-September 1, 1919 (Reel 57)
      - October 14, 1919-August 18, 1920 (Reel 58)
      - July 17, 1924-August 20, 1926 (Reel 58)
      - October 13, 1926-January 26, 1931 (Reel 58)
      - January 14, 1943-January 14, 1961 (Reel 58)
    - Annual reports 1920-1927 (Reel 58)
    - Letters (Reel 58)
    - Rules (Reel 58)
    - Minute book (Finnish Temperance Home)
      - May 24, 1929-February 21, 1930 (Reel 58)
  - The Finnish Workers' Illness and Funeral Aid Organization, Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Minute books
      - July 15, 1906-June 18, 1911 (Reel 58)
      - April 16, 1911-July 22, 1916 (Reel 59)
      - September 30, 1906-August 20, 1916 (Reel 59)
      - September 3, 1916-June 28, 1919 (Reel 59)
      - September 27, 1919-February 21, 1925 (Reel 59)
      - January 3, 1920-July 9, 1932 (Reel 59)
      - August 3, 1929-August 10, 1946 (Reel 59)
      - January 15, 1932-June 29, 1935 (Reel 59)
      - July 13, 1935-December 30, 1938 (Reel 59)
      - January 14, 1939-July 19, 1951 (Reel 59)
  - The Finnish Workers' Illness and Funeral Aid Organization, Monessen, Pennsylvania (Weirton, Pa. Chapter)
    - Minute books
      - March 28, 1915-June 10, 1928 (Reel 60)
      - July 8, 1928-March 25, 1945 (Reel 60)
  - Temperance Society Voiton Lippu [The Flag of Victory], Monessen, Pennsylvania
    - Minute books
      - March 5, 1905-September 1, 1907 (Reel 60)
      - September 8, 1907-September 3, 1911 (Reel 60)
      - September 10, 1911-March 31, 1912 (Reel 61)
      - April 7, 1912-May 23, 1915 (Reel 61)
      - May 30, 1915-September 1, 1918 (Reel 61)
      - July 17, 1921-February 1, 1926 (Reel 61)
  - The Finnish-American Historical Society of Iron County, Michigan
    - Minute books
      - June 4, 1938-January 11, 1951 (Reel 62)
      - February 4, 1951-January 30, 1955 (Reel 62)
      - March 8, 1955-July 10, 1962 (Reel 62)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Cobalt, Ontario, Canada
    - Minute book
      - May 13, 1917-February 26, 1919 (Reel 62)
  - Lännen Lähtysliitto [The Mission League of the West], Astoria, Oregon
    - Minute books
      - April 10, 1937-March 21, 1959 (Reel 62)
      - June 20, 1928-June 4, 1953 (Reel 62)
  - The Families of the ministers in the Eastern Section of Suomi Synod
    - Minute book
      - October 14, 1946-October 12, 1962 (Reel 63)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Cave Hill
    - Minute book
      - December 15, 1918-February 7, 1964 (Reel 63)
  - Temperance Society Tähti [Star], Clarksburg, West Virginia
    - Minute book
      - March 9, 1918-September 7, 1942 (Reel 63)
  - Temperance Society Elämän Toivo [The Hope of Life], Weirton, West Virginia
    - Minute books
      - July 13, 1912-February 10, 1918 (Reel 63)
      - February 17, 1918-July 1, 1923 (Reel 63)
  - Temperance Society Pohjan Leimu [The Flame of the North], Soudan, Minnesota
    - Minute books
      - May 30, 1886-August 19, 1900 (Reel 64)
      - September 2, 1900-June 18, 1905 (Reel 64)
      - October 30, 1921-May 6, 1923 (Reel 65)
      - 1923-1934 (Reel 65)
      - July 20, 1934-January 28, 1953 (Reel 65)
  - Temperance Society Rantakorven Kukka [The Flower of the Wilderness Beach], Buhl, Minnesota
    - Minute books
      - March 12, 1905-May 14, 1911 (Reel 65)
      - May 21, 1911-November 21, 1915 (Reel 65)
  - Finnish Lutheran Congregation of Virginia, Minnesota
    - Minute book (sewing circle)
      - December 30, 1931-December 17, 1941 (Reel 65)
  - Temperance Society Valon Leimu [The Flame of the Light], Rockport, Massachusetts
    - Minute books
      - April 8, 1899-June 7, 1903 (Reel 66)
      - June 28, 1903-April 8, 1906 (Reel 66)
      - April 15, 1906-June 25, 1911 (Reel 66)
      - July 2, 1911-February 4, 1917 (Reel 66)
      - February 11, 1917-April 27, 1924 (Reel 66)
      - July 6, 1924-November 14, 1926 (Reel 67)